{
    "id": "83b6e8bdefac40d2964b1381e61cabd8",
    "title": "Editing Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "They went out despite of the rain.",
            "description": "You have to use despite or in spite of.",
            "answers": [
                "out",
                "of",
                "the"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f89d1fe066e4e0f911724dd4796508a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Raju, who is my cousin, he is a painter.",
            "description": "The relative pronoun acts as the subject or object of the verb in the relative clause.",
            "answers": [
                "who",
                "he",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "159a03d8fbd84832b860a5dbc3cf94ee"
        },
        {
            "question": "No matter what that I do, nothing seems to work.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "what",
                "that",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "c0313372685e4c5b8b1f808f2cb4192f"
        },
        {
            "question": "We discussed about his problems when we met yesterday.",
            "description": "Discuss is one of those verbs that are not followed by a preposition.",
            "answers": [
                "about",
                "when",
                "his"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "61d2dbe1ece74920b914c7a647398f76"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy that you find over there he is my son.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "over",
                "he"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "08b48346766845f5b845628a98831f7b"
        },
        {
            "question": "I have had an unforgettable experience yesterday.",
            "description": "We cannot use the present perfect with past time expressions. ",
            "answers": [
                "have",
                "had",
                "an"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2695ede1b9684708bc20613be951f528"
        },
        {
            "question": "I want that you to tell me what happened.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "that",
                "you",
                "me"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ac92b5225fc2429fba058e6ebdc98b39"
        },
        {
            "question": "As you know that I work very hard.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "that",
                "Either can be removed"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1713ab63ed744ff6a3b2846c39b79f57"
        },
        {
            "question": "He plays the hockey for a local team.",
            "description": "We say hockey, not the hockey.",
            "answers": [
                "the",
                "a"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "417dcebb50694dd69e4b1137e09d9274"
        },
        {
            "question": "What a terrible weather we are having.",
            "description": "Weather is uncountable. We cannot use a with it. ",
            "answers": [
                "a",
                "having",
                "what"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "6e4dc5707ba54aebb5576a03ad9e76b1"
        },
        {
            "question": "I had left my keys on the table.",
            "description": "To simply state that we did something in the past, use the simple past.",
            "answers": [
                "had",
                "on",
                "left"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "56ef097a03bc4efbb2dee613958683c5"
        },
        {
            "question": "She resembles of her mother.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "of",
                "her"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "ff199b58674d4d04a614789308315142"
        }
    ]
}